http://dpsscotland.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Digital Print Scotland are committed to:
* protecting the personal information you give us
* telling you how we use the information we gather about you
* getting your consent to our disclosure of your personal information.
Our privacy policy is set out in detail below. Any changes to this policy will be posted here. When we refer to “we”, “our” or “us” in this policy we mean the activities of Digital Print Scotland.
* We want to offer you a service which you want to use. We may use information about you to help us customise our site to improve its usefulness to you.
* We compile anonymous records of user trends which we make use of ourselves. We do not pass these to unconnected parties.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU?
* We may collect information from you when you fill in an online registration form for any of our web site services, (e.g., advisory services etc.). We may also collect information you give us over the telephone or in written or other communications. The type of information we will collect includes, for example, your name, mailing address, email address and telephone numbers.
* We collect information about your use of our sites’ web site services through “cookies”. Cookies are blocks of text placed in files on your computer’s hard drive when you visit a website which contain information to identify you. A cookie does not contain any personal information you have provided us with, except your user name or email address, unless the cookie is attached to personal information collected another way, such as by means of your online quotation form.
EU & UK COOKIE LAW
The EU Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) introduced legislation regarding the use of cookies on websites. This legislation came into effect on 26th May 2012 and is intended to allow users to be aware if a site is using cookies and to be able to approve the use of certain cookies that may be used to identify or track browsing behaviour.
This site does not rely on cookies to operate properly however our ISP’s hosting server logs do collect visitor some data and that is shared with Google Analytics which we use to help us analyse visitor data with a view to enhancing our website and the users experience.
This data is not identifiable to any particular person or machine. If you do not agree to this, please adjust your browser settings or do not use this site.
YOUR CONSENT
By using this website you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information in accordance with our privacy policy as set out. If you subsequently decide you no longer wish to receive information from us, please notify us by email at the following address: enquiries@dpsscotland.com
HOW WE ENSURE PRIVACY IS MAINTAINED
* We endeavour to ensure that your data is stored securely and to prevent unauthorised access. We have security measures in place to protect your information which we monitor regularly. Unfortunately, despite our measures, because of the nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that your information will remain at all times 100% secure. The continuing efforts of hackers to defeat even the newest of security systems means that we can never give such a guarantee.
* Please be aware that if you disclose information on chat areas, forums or other public services it may be possible for other people to use this information. We are not responsible for the disclosure of any information you post in this way.
* Our policy is to comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 and all other legislation which governs the maintenance of privacy in your information. We also require compliance with such legislation by third parties with whom we have arrangements to offer goods or services through our web sites.
* Our web sites provide a number of links to web sites not operated by us or by companies associated with us. We take no responsibility for the use of any information about you which is collected as a result of your use of these web sites and this privacy policy does not extend to any web site operated by anybody other than us.
Cookies are being used on this site. Please agree to accept these cookies to enjoy the full benefits of the site’s featuresAcceptDeclineMore info
